Marvin C. Griffin papers, Inclusive: 1940-2011, undated, Bulk: 1960-1999, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Audio-Visual Materials, 1940-2010, undated; 4
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 93 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 94 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 95 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 96 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 97 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 98 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 63 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 99 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 53 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 100 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 25 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 101 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 24 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 102 OVZ)
  - Audio Recordings: Audio Cassettes, 23 tapes, 1971-2010, undated (Box 103 OVZ)